<resources>
    <string name="app_name">C.U.T Student</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="appversion">1.0</string>

    <string name="developer">Kinsley Kajiva</string>
    <!---->
    <string-array name="classtime_arrays">
        <item>07:00 - 09:00</item>
        <item>09:15 - 11:15</item>
        <item>11:30 - 13:30</item>
        <item>13:45 - 15:45</item>
        <item>16:00 - 18:00</item>
        <item>18:15 - 20:15</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="ClassVenue">
        <item>Great Hall</item>
        <item>Computer lab 1</item>
        <item>Computer lab 2</item>
        <item>Unix lab</item>

    </string-array>
    <!---->
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">PREV</string>
    <string name="start">Done.</string>
    <string name="slide_1_title">Hello</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Welcome To Chinhoyi University Student App.</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">App SetUP</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Customise the app according to your Undergraduate Programme.\nClick Next.</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title"></string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">After SetUp Click Next</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">All Done.</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Please Enjoy Using Our Student App.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome_setup">WelcomeSetup</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="install">Install</string>
    <string name="customactivityoncrash_error_activity_error_occurred_explanation">An unexpected error occurred.\nSorry for the inconvenience.</string>
    <string name="AboutApp">
        C.U.T Student App is a Chinhoyi University Student Android Application developed to help students keep track of their studies.\n\n
        The Student App is basically a Timetable app that comes with features like setting adding or creating a Lecture and  Tutorials,making Lecture or Tutorial Reminders(Alarms).
        \n\n
        The application also comes with the message receiving ability.\n\n
        Please do note that data loaded from server or internet can change at any time this include your TimeTable,Exam-Timetable.
        \n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
        Developed by Kinsley  Kajiva &#8211;(ICT Student).
    </string>
    <string name="new_version">Please download a new version to enjoy newer features. </string>
    <string name="version_warning">Please your advised that this version will soon be Obsolete.Consider upgrading.</string>
<string name="library_licence">
        Please do note we the developers of Chinhoyi University Student App do by every right acknowledge Apache License of every library we have used in our App! \n\n

    Below is a list of all used library:\n\n
    • Square Up - okhttp 3\n
    • Bumptech  - glide \n
    • Realm.io - realm.io.java \n
    • Fabric.io - crashlytics\n
    • Google  - android.support Libraries,Firebase\n
    • Jon Finerty - Once\n
    • Douglas Nassif Roma Junior - simple-tooltip\n
    • Keepsafe Software Inc - taptargetview\n
    • flipkart-incubator - circular-image\n\n\n

        Copyright 2016 All Third Party Library\n

        Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");\n
        you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n
        You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\n

           http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\n

        Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
        distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
        WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
        See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
        limitations under the License.
    \n\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="known_Bugs">
    Here is a list of all known possible bugs that users may feel or see as they use the application.\n\n
    These bugs may not be causing any run-time exceptions but they still need correcting.\n\n
    • When renaming the tabs to from the settings sections it may occur that when a user taps
    the renaming option twice in a activity session the renaming code may wipe out the tab titles hence the tabs
    and their content.\n\n
    • This one is for the developer who may want to update the realm data base , do note that when ever you update the data base or library
    version some methods may be rendered old or deprecated so go through the CRUD class found DBAccess package, so this could affect the
    performance of the whole application.\n\n
    • Also in updating the code do consider redoing the CRUD class found in DBAccess package to pass the Realm object to
    the methods in need or in question as i may think that write operations at the moment may be slow than reading operations.\n\n
    • When switching from Class TimeTable to Examinations TimeTable as you would have noticed that the whole applications closes
    and it resets all of the variables this has various advantages.I do hope there will another way of switching and that resets
    several app runtime conditions. As you would switch from these TimeTables one of the two has to be rendered invalid to use
    whilst using the other one.\n\n
    • As of API 25 and below there is no known way of removing app shortcut at the users home screen(Please Note: this is subject to the
    users Theme that they have at the moment of using the app).So at the moment if users clear the app cache that also clears the app
    timetable please do know all preferences or temporary database will be wiped out so ,another short-cut will be  created it may annoy
    the user so by any means in new API (25 + ) do take care of this.\n
    \n\n
    • Thus All.
    </string>
    <string name="study_tip_credit_1">
        https://www.reading.ac.uk
    </string>
     <string name="study_tip_credit_2">
       http://slc.berkeley.edu \n http://centuracollege.edu
    </string>
</resources>
